yroo.com 2015-09-12

# Privacy Policy | yroo

RETAILCOMMON Inc., the owner of yroo.com (“yroo.com,” “us” or “we”), owns and operates the yroo.com website (the “Web Site”) and the services related to or offered on the Web Site (the “Services”).

Your privacy and the respectful and responsible handling of your personal information is very important to us. The purpose of this privacy policy (the “Policy”) is to outline the types of information that may be collected about you when visiting the Web Site, how that information will be used and disclosed, and how you can control, correct and update the information.

Each visit to the Web Site or use of the Services constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of the Policy. Providing personal information or authorizing a third party to disclose personal information to us signifies your consent to yroo.com’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.

For the purposes of this Policy, “personal information” means information that can identify an individual directly or through other reasonably available means. The meaning of “personal information” shall be interpreted in a manner that conforms with the minimum requirements of applicable provincial and federal privacy legislation.

## 1\. Our Privacy Principles

Type of Personal Information Collected

The type of information we collect is linked to the purposes. For instance, when you sign up to be a Member, we may collect your name, email address, and other payment information as well as information about the products or services you view or purchase. If you are part of a referral program we keep track of who you refer and who refers you (as applicable). In addition, we sometimes host contests, so we will collect information as set forth in the contest rules.

Identifying Purposes and Obtaining Your Consent

The purposes for which we collect personal information are mostly what you would reasonably expect. Where it is not reasonably evident why we’re collecting information, we would identify the purposes for collecting your personal information at or before the time it is collected. We will not collect, use or disclose your personal information without your informed consent, unless required or permitted to do so by law.

To provide to you a few example of why we collect personal information, we collect, use and disclose personal information about you so we can:

  * maintain and manage our membership;
  * account for reward points or cash back earned under your account;
  * allocate cash back;
  * process payments; and
  * target advertisements to make the Web Site and/or Services more personal and useful to you. 

We may also use your personal information to communicate with you about new products, Services, offerings or other information we reasonably believe may be useful to you.

## 2\. Limiting Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Information Gathered and Used

We collect personal information by fair and lawful means and limit collection to that information which is reasonably necessary for the purposes identified in this Policy.

The choice to provide us with your personal information, either directly or through a third party, is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular information may limit our ability to provide you with some of our products or Services.

How your Information is Collected

Most of the personal information we collect will be done online. However, personal information may also be collected in a number of ways, including: over the phone, by mail or, yes, even by fax if necessary (and such fax machines exist). We may also collect personal information from third parties who you have authorized to disclose personal information to us (for instance, our Affiliate Stores will have information on your purchases and that information may be provided to us if necessary to audit transactions and ensure rewards are properly allocated).

We make every reasonable effort to ensure that those third parties that disclose your personal information to us have first obtained your consent. If you believe that a third party has inappropriately disclosed your personal information to us, please contact that third party directly. If the third party does not sufficiently respond to your inquiries, please let us know immediately.

Your personal information will only be used or disclosed in accordance with the purposes for which it was collected, unless you have otherwise consented and except where required or permitted by law.

Web cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer from a webpage to keep track of information about your browsing on that Web Site. Cookies are essential to our ability to track what you’ve viewed and your purchases. We cannot offer the Services or allocate rewards or cash back without cookies being installed in your system.

In addition, through the use of web cookies, we may monitor the ads you see and the number of times you view them. The use of cookies also allows us to capture standard web traffic information, such as the time and date you visited our Web Site, your IP address, and your browser information.

Information from Social Media. If you access or log-in to the yroo Service through a social media service or connect yroo to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Services through social media services or when you connect a Service to social media services, you are authorizing yroo to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Disclosure to Third Parties

From time to time we may share your personal information with third parties, as approved by you and/or as described in this Policy. Use of this Web Site and/or Services signifies your consent to yroo.com’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.

The type of information we are legally required to disclose may relate to criminal investigations or government tax reporting requirements. In some instances, such as a legal proceeding or court order, we may also be required to disclose your personal information to authorities. Only the information specifically requested is disclosed and we take precautions to satisfy ourselves that the authorities that are making the disclosure request have legitimate grounds to do so.

Your personal information may be disclosed in situations where we are legally permitted to do so, such as in the course of employing reasonable and legal methods to enforce your rights or to investigate suspicion of unlawful activities. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of ourselves and others.

You also understand and agree that we may use your personal information and disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with the proposed or actual financing, insuring, sale, securitization, assignment or other disposal of all or part of our business or assets (including accounts) for the purposes of evaluating and/or performing the proposed transaction. These purposes may include, for example, permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed or continue with the transaction, fulfilling any reporting or audit requirements to such parties, and/or disclosing personal information as part of concluding a sale or transfer of assets. Our successors and assigns may collect, use and disclose your personal information for substantially the same purposes as those set out in this Policy. In the event the transaction does not go through, we will require, by contract, the other party or parties to the transaction not to use or disclose your personal information in any manner whatsoever for any purpose, and to return or destroy such personal information.

Personal information may also be disclosed to service providers and/or third-party contractors who we work with and/or employ on our behalf to help operate yroo.com, the Web Site and/or the Services.

Information that cannot be used to reasonably identify an individual (“Anonymous Information”) may be used in aggregate form, combined with other users’ Anonymous Information, and shared with third parties.

Personal information collected during a promotion, contest, sweepstake or poll (“Promotion”), in part or in its entirety, may be disclosed publicly and/or to third parties, as disclosed in the Promotion rules at the time of collection. We do not take responsibility for the privacy policy or practices of any third party. Upon participation in any Promotion, you are subject to any official rules, terms and conditions of that Promotion.

Some or all of your personal information may be shared with Licensors of the Web Site and/or Services. This Policy does not cover the privacy policies or practices of the Licensors.

Personal Information may also be collected and shared with third-party Sponsors, Merchants and/or Vendors. A notice at the time of collection of Personal Information on behalf of a Sponsor will be provided to you along with a link to the Sponsor’s privacy policy.

Any information that you share and make publicly available may be made available to all users and third parties. We are not responsible for any information that you share, and your use of the Web Site and/or Services constitutes your acceptance of any risk involved in your disclosure of such information.

Keeping your Information Accurate

We make every reasonable effort to keep your personal information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary. If desired, you may verify the accuracy and completeness of your personal information in our records.

Despite our best efforts, errors sometimes do occur. Should you identify any incorrect or out-of-date information in your file, we will remedy any such errors on a timely basis. In the event that inaccurate information is mistakenly sent to a third party, we will communicate relevant changes to the third party where appropriate.

Please be aware that we may retain some or all of your Personal information in accordance with our Data Retention Policy, and such Personal information provided in accordance with this Policy may remain within our databases, access logs and/or other records. yroo.com is not responsible for correcting, updating or removing any of your Personal Information contained in any third-party’s lists or databases that was provide in accordance with this Policy.

Childrens’ Information

The Web Site and Services are not directed toward, nor intended for, individuals under the age of 18. Individuals under the age of 18 should not register for the Web Site and/or Services, or provide any personal information. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from individuals under the age of 18. Parents and/or legal guardians of children under the age of 18 who believe their child has registered and/or provided any personal information should contact us at support@yroo.com so that we may delete and remove any such personal information.

## 3\. Protecting Your Personal Information

Access to your Information within yroo.com

Access to private, sensitive and confidential information, including your personal information, is restricted to authorized employees with legitimate business reasons. For example, when responding to customer enquiries, employees will need to access your information to verify your identity and to properly assist you.

We require all of our employees to abide by yroo.com’s privacy standards. Our employees understand the importance of keeping your information private. Employees are strictly prohibited from accessing or disclosing personal information without authorization. All employees are expected to maintain the confidentiality of personal information at all times and failure to do so will result in appropriate disciplinary measures including dismissal.

Disposal and Retention

Except as otherwise permitted or required by law, your personal information will be retained for so long as is reasonably necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected and for a period of time reasonably necessary to conform with legal obligations and to protect our rights and obligations.

Safeguarding your Information

To ensure that your personal information is protected, we utilize security safeguards that are on par with the industry standard. We use modern technologies to ensure that your confidential information is not compromised. Our server environment and firewall infrastructure are well-maintained and our security practices are reviewed on a regular basis.

We keep electronic customer files in a highly-secured environment with restricted access. Paper-based files are stored in locked filing cabinets to which access is also restricted.

We use Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) and 128-bit encryption technologies to enhance security for the secured areas of our Web Site. SSL protects and maintains the security of messages transmitted over the Internet. SSL scrambles your data into an unreadable format, preventing unauthorized access by others.

## 4\. Web Sites Governed by this Privacy Policy

Our Web Site (yroo.com) is governed by the provisions and practices stated in this Policy. Our Web Site may contain links to third-party web sites that are not governed by this Policy. Although we endeavour to only link to web sites that share our commitment to your privacy, please be aware that this Policy will no longer apply once you leave our web sites and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party web sites. We therefore suggest that you closely examine the respective privacy policies of third-party web sites to learn how they collect, use and disclose your personal information.

Addressing Your Inquiries and Concerns

We are happy to provide you with a copy of this Policy and to discuss any of its content with you.

Upon request, we will also inform you of: the type of personal information we have collected; how your personal information has been used; and any third parties to whom your personal information has been disclosed.

Please direct all questions or enquiries by email to support@yroo.com

## 5\. Updating this Privacy Policy

Any changes to our privacy standards and information handling practices will be reflected in this Policy in a timely manner. yroo.com reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any modifications. To determine when this Policy was last updated, please refer to the modification date at the bottom of this Policy. All material changes to this Privacy Policy shall be effective thirty (30) days after the date notice of such changes were posted on our Web Site. Each visit to the Web Site or use of the Services constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of the Policy. Providing personal information or authorizing a third party to disclose personal information to us signifies your consent to yroo.com’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.

## 6\. Governing Law

This Policy and all related matters are governed solely by the laws of the Province of Ontario and the applicable federal laws of Canada.

yroo.com may perform activities outside of Canada through third parties, such as Affiliate Stores and third party processing agents. You acknowledge and agree that, as a result, your personal information may be processed, used, stored or accessed in other countries and may be subject to the laws of those countries. For example, information may be disclosed in response to valid demands or requests from government authorities, courts, or law enforcement in other countries. In particular, information that is processed, used, stored or accessed in the United States may be subject to the Patriot Act and applicable anti-terrorism legislation, together with other legislation applicable within the United States.

Last revised Tuesday, January 27, 2015

21426181.2
